[
  {
    "Front": "θάλαττα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: hav"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θάνατος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: død"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θαρρέω",
    "Back": " vb.: er ved godt mod"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θαυµάζω",
    "Back": " vb.: beundrer, undrer mig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θαυµάσιος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: forunderlig,"
  },
  {
    "Front": "beundringsværdig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θαυµαστός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: forunderlig,"
  },
  {
    "Front": "beundringsværdig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεά",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: gudinde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεάοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: betragter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θέατρον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: teater"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεῖος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: guddommelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θέλω",
    "Back": " vb. (sml. ἐθέλω): vil"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: gud"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεραπεύω",
    "Back": " vb.: betjener, behandler"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θεράπων",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: tjener"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θερµός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: varm"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θέρος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: sommer"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θῆλυς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: kvindelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θηρίον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: dyr (vildt)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θνητός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: dødelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θυγάτηρ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: datter"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θυµός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: sind, mod, engagement"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θύρα",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: dør"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θυσία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: ofring"
  },
  {
    "Front": "θύω",
    "Back": " vb.: ofrer"
  }
]